{
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "0c3fbad3-0ef0-4dd5-b8b7-b4bf64f3577c",
      "front": "Atom",
      "back": "Atom",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "3eca62dc-d1c9-4e6f-a08a-6d19e2258941",
      "front": "Molecule",
      "back": "Molekul",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "7f4b1f88-7d2d-4e7d-8b66-486e188a89be",
      "front": "Cell",
      "back": "Sel",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "af46f673-d281-4b5d-95cd-2361ebd79b82",
      "front": "Tissue",
      "back": "Jaringan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "c812b05c-4672-4d76-ae42-a5fbf51fb37a",
      "front": "Organ",
      "back": "Organ",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "e6ceae0e-5c3a-47e7-ae35-c2aa5e33f0a2",
      "front": "Nucleus",
      "back": "Inti sel / Nukleus",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "fbcc43de-f7b6-411c-aa7c-fb00730b0e1d",
      "front": "Diffusion",
      "back": "Difusi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "5b9cf726-75c9-4418-beec-e8262dd2de59",
      "front": "Enzyme",
      "back": "Enzim",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "df18758e-4ef4-4aaa-867e-33b59b950884",
      "front": "Photosynthesis",
      "back": "Fotosintesis",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "b79ebf51-d4c3-4476-a32e-4c8bd2ff1cca",
      "front": "Ecology",
      "back": "Ekologi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "e7bec0ad-591f-4db5-bd53-ee5fb6f33276",
      "front": "Force",
      "back": "Gaya",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "98f78829-6666-4fa8-809d-eb53b74e2ade",
      "front": "Velocity",
      "back": "Kecepatan (arah & nilai)",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "b4a0c4ef-af64-4cfa-bbe5-241f71a479d4",
      "front": "Acceleration",
      "back": "Percepatan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "84cfb5c9-b4ee-48f5-9c25-e6b0197e96e8",
      "front": "Energy",
      "back": "Energi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "89e56d31-1dc5-4b78-afce-1ca8d7b5b0ad",
      "front": "Work",
      "back": "Usaha",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "22b4bc6b-aa12-45e1-b841-1a1b02081bcf",
      "front": "Power",
      "back": "Daya",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "68a05f58-468e-42b2-afb3-9a3b75d042ec",
      "front": "Momentum",
      "back": "Momentum",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "4cae2981-4c2e-4f3c-a4a5-89c08d2c0c72",
      "front": "Wave",
      "back": "Gelombang",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "fd1614a7-18a3-4d72-9d42-2d6cbb7ccb6e",
      "front": "Frequency",
      "back": "Frekuensi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "c6ad7355-a4cd-491d-92af-3f6bda7c6013",
      "front": "Amplitude",
      "back": "Amplitudo",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "d25519f8-f5d9-4721-b02a-5f9c91f5c52f",
      "front": "Electric Current",
      "back": "Arus listrik",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "29bb1270-d9e0-49e8-b430-1e0c65561b57",
      "front": "Voltage",
      "back": "Tegangan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "4fcfb8d8-4c48-4e41-8cf5-f8b52665c274",
      "front": "Resistance",
      "back": "Hambatan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "3b8c97b9-1698-4f7f-980d-8887bb5f9e11",
      "front": "Magnetism",
      "back": "Kemagnetan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "4f33eaae-d70c-4b73-b246-9cd9e99bfb05",
      "front": "Refraction",
      "back": "Pembiasan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "36f41d00-91a5-4ef0-9e58-2c09130ad13b",
      "front": "Chemical Reaction",
      "back": "Reaksi kimia",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "1890e54f-2663-4e07-bbad-4e873a8d4c84",
      "front": "Acid",
      "back": "Asam",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "19cf4f42-239e-46cf-9f55-8ccc40c7e7df",
      "front": "Base",
      "back": "Basa",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "8e3bf6f1-6317-41e6-b2a9-1b08b39e1e2e",
      "front": "Salt",
      "back": "Garam",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "9564e704-936a-4ba9-bf2c-ae90ec9b5fb7",
      "front": "Solution",
      "back": "Larutan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "ce3d54a3-80b8-46c8-83f2-863993da0b0e",
      "front": "Evaporation",
      "back": "Penguapan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "8571f7c0-7d0f-4b06-9fa4-b41b73de652d",
      "front": "Condensation",
      "back": "Kondensasi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "a919e5a1-138b-4429-8e29-19ed102e9f1c",
      "front": "Distillation",
      "back": "Distilasi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "68542e6f-d704-4f4c-a05b-21fc054d900f",
      "front": "Oxidation",
      "back": "Oksidasi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "e8b0a9b2-a019-4b71-857e-b548c8d5baf6",
      "front": "Reduction",
      "back": "Reduksi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "a262699f-5b82-4e2a-9658-d11f1c797305",
      "front": "Equation",
      "back": "Persamaan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "77551819-8935-4a23-86e4-1a980dc9057c",
      "front": "Variable",
      "back": "Variabel",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "d7f1ae82-fdd3-4a6e-86e4-4fd12439c57e",
      "front": "Function",
      "back": "Fungsi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "a7e3f03d-b5a6-417d-8f15-a2e7271cbf53",
      "front": "Derivative",
      "back": "Turunan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "ce80cbc3-0024-4dc0-ad46-daf2e2188a98",
      "front": "Integral",
      "back": "Integral",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "7d4f4271-f73a-4e6d-9ea7-d5c6571b995a",
      "front": "Probability",
      "back": "Probabilitas",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "872f13c4-fd5d-4345-91c2-d030605eecf4",
      "front": "Statistics",
      "back": "Statistika",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "0447fa54-848f-46ee-bb32-9590cf994f7b",
      "front": "Vector",
      "back": "Vektor",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "21e9de18-55ae-4620-bf43-6f02578bcb91",
      "front": "Matrix",
      "back": "Matriks",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "fbcd3989-730d-4874-a759-89b9c688c335",
      "front": "Geometry",
      "back": "Geometri",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "ea17bb64-1b52-45c2-863c-a2e70dc2ff2c",
      "front": "Geography",
      "back": "Geografi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "1d44698d-b2dc-44fc-b2f5-67c36dd8b12f",
      "front": "Climate",
      "back": "Iklim",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "bff38a75-27fb-4c8a-929c-e30547c939c6",
      "front": "Weather",
      "back": "Cuaca",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "4a134786-b952-40ad-af75-b516a80dd427",
      "front": "Continent",
      "back": "Benua",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "739bffe0-08b8-4bcd-9a19-9cec02b91735",
      "front": "Latitude",
      "back": "Garis lintang",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "364515de-d464-4dbf-bdd0-feb3544ba85c",
      "front": "Longitude",
      "back": "Garis bujur",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "5689d356-70c9-4dde-9e3b-7e88fe019ca3",
      "front": "Erosion",
      "back": "Erosi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "676957c7-d87f-4e54-a19b-e158ae71ed7a",
      "front": "Deposition",
      "back": "Sedimentasi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "d06cb34d-f764-4905-aa1b-1ee98eb2428c",
      "front": "Mountain",
      "back": "Gunung",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "c39160ab-46f8-4794-9067-d81b970873a3",
      "front": "River",
      "back": "Sungai",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "c51b6eca-bc4b-4a91-bb6d-7b3942fabbd8",
      "front": "Economy",
      "back": "Ekonomi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "ecc7a7cd-38fb-4c4e-b7c2-3d8a834f678d",
      "front": "Inflation",
      "back": "Inflasi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "ae3bfc45-c53f-4873-8fc4-e28c37b99461",
      "front": "Demand",
      "back": "Permintaan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "6bd031e2-c3ee-4a33-b359-aa36b148801f",
      "front": "Supply",
      "back": "Penawaran",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "cd49f143-ad35-42e0-9994-05bb32744d86",
      "front": "Market",
      "back": "Pasar",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "50cca70b-f002-4cc7-bc6c-06d1dd90c019",
      "front": "Capital",
      "back": "Modal",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "13f4e39d-1f4f-49d0-92fc-98ad5c3d2a7a",
      "front": "Profit",
      "back": "Keuntungan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "13630042-59df-4836-993d-2e2f5e1b16b2",
      "front": "Loss",
      "back": "Kerugian",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "fa7857f1-10b0-4e94-8a96-8a1a7771a146",
      "front": "Investment",
      "back": "Investasi",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "47850a82-fd7e-4a3a-ac52-07d49438cbc8",
      "front": "Tax",
      "back": "Pajak",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "68044e89-be45-4416-ab13-3ff4cc116b9d",
      "front": "Grammar",
      "back": "Tata bahasa",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "6e7ba110-6183-4cae-b188-a9bb9caad1dc",
      "front": "Paragraph",
      "back": "Paragraf",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "07dc2f5a-2e08-4254-9b7e-cd37a9e06760",
      "front": "Sentence",
      "back": "Kalimat",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "91abf14b-2577-4052-9a33-8a79bdbb9cf4",
      "front": "Vocabulary",
      "back": "Kosakata",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    },
    {
      "id": "c3205a4b-a8c6-4d35-b61e-30a532d0e31a",
      "front": "Pronunciation",
      "back": "Pengucapan",
      "interval": 1,
      "ease_factor": 2.5,
      "step": 1,
      "due": "2025-11-18T07:19:11.606520+00:00",
      "first_time": true
    }
  ]
}